

# CONTACT

- **\*** +95-977-545-8313
- Sanchaung Township, Yangon
- swanhtet1230@gmail.com
- sh-portfolio.onrender.com
- swanhtethein

# SOFT SKILLS



**Project Planning** 



Time Management



Communication



Researching

### LANGUAGE

- English
- Burmese

# Swan Htet Hein

Junior Web Developer

# **PROFILE**

I am currently a student and I received my HND in computing at Gusto University on July 11, 2022, and I intend to continue my education abroad for my Bachelor's degree in 2023.

During my year, in one of the NGO groups, I gained leadership experience. While trying for my Diploma, I successfully completed some hardware and software-based subjects and used them to create some projects' kind as Web, IoT projects, networking, and cloud computing practices.

After that, I joined an NGO class to learn about basic Research-Based Critical Thinking & Analysis and after that period I kept in touch with Crypto currency and NFT. However, I'm back to my career, web development at the end of 2022, I joined Wun Wun Lat Education, which teaches the basics of web development for advancement.

I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, curious about the new technic related with my career. Even though I am still taking the advanced class, I already have the ability and knowledge of the beginner class, because they also provide me with on-the-job training, because I am a temporary class. Due to my knowledge background, I'm also turned off for some backend development.

#### MY EXPERTISE

HTML5/CSS3	bootstrap	Javascript	Figma
Cloud-Computing	Programming basic	Photoshop CS6	

## **EDUCATION**

# Pyin Nyar San Eain Private High School

#### **Matriculation Examination**

I passed the matriculation examination and received either Diploma A or Diploma B allowed to continue education at university in 2018 - 2019.

# • GUSTO University

# **Higher National Diploma in Computing**

While trying to work on my diploma, it offers courses in Basic Web Development, IoT, Networking, and Cloud Computing, in addition to Fundamental and Advanced programming and Soft-skills. 2023 February, I earned my Higher National Diploma in computing with Grade Distinction.

### Hysan Education

### English4Skills (Upper Intermediate)

I attended Hysan Education, which helps students improve their English fluency and qualification. It did take more than 6 months, but I was able to develop my skills and knowledge as well as English status as a result of their activities and coursework.

# (yaung Thar Association

# Research-Based Critical Thinking & Analysis Course

This course helped me develop my research skills and highlighted actual basic research processes. I received certification for having completed my research proposal on NFT and Crypto Currency in July 2022.

#### Wun Wun Lat Education

#### **Web Development Basic to Advanced**

In this course, I can focus on my professional part and advance from basic to advanced. They offered fundamental and front-end subjects such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and Figma, as well as advanced courses such as database structure, Laval Power shell and Linux command Laravel Framework, Docker Postman, NodeJS, ExpressJs, and ReactJs.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER** 

Wun Wun Lat - IT Solutions 2022 - 2023

I assisted senior developers in designing and coding website features using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. And then I contributed to the development of web applications with PHP language. I improved website performance by optimizing images and improving page load time and I developed Website using WordPress themes and plugins.

I used to assist in migrating websites from one server to another and I collaborated with designers and other team members to understand project requirements and provide solutions. I version Control of Git and content Management System with WordPress.

Team Leader & Co-founder

IMReading Organization 2020-2021

As a leader in a non-profit organization (Reading Club) and assisted in training members to develop a reading habit, among other things. I also guided the group volunteers and provided fan activities to the organization's audience as a CO-founder. Morevoer, I used to make a celebration with other organizations like meditation and had done group work projects.

IOT Project(Solo Project)

GUSTO University 2022 - 2023

I have done a home system project (fire alarm PD) with IoT infrastructure equipment. As for the development coding language, I chose C# once and it was created for both online and practical projects. I managed up and presented to University completely all the tasks and testing errors by myself and earned Distinction grade in this subject.